Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-1641. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1641, Boston, Massachusetts -1943 / Lodge No. 1641, Fruit and Produce Lodge, West Medford, Massachusetts, 1937-1942 (Box 146, Folder 38)
      Disbanded Jan. 19, 1943
  - Sub-Series 235-1646. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1646, H. Harris Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1953-1956 (Box 146, Folder 39)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 840, Boston, Massachusetts, effective Oct. 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-1647. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1647, National Carloading Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1938-1962 (Box 146, Folder 40)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1605, Detroit, Michigan effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1648. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1648, Bancroft Lodge, Worcester, Massachusetts, 1947-1962 (Box 146, Folder 41)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1600, Springfield, Massachusetts, effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1700. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1700 (formerly No. 6259, changed Dec. 1960), Santa Fe Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1943-1963 (Box 146, Folder 42)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 618, Chicago, Illinois, effective Oct. 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1702. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1702 (formerly No. 6323, changed Dec. 1960), Robinhood Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1947-1963 (Box 146, Folder 43)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 318, Chicago, Illinois, effective Oct. 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1703. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1703 (formerly No. 6170, changed 1961), Lockfield Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1943-1964 (Box 146, Folder 44)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 92, Indianapolis, Indiana, effective Jan. 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-1704. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1704 (formerly No. 6264, changed 1960), Evansville, Indiana, 1944-1962 (Box 146, Folder 45)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 860, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1705. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1705 (formerly No. 6330, changed 1961), Reed Taylor Lodge, Hammond, Indiana, 1948-1962 (Box 146, Folder 46)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 357, effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1707. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1707 (formerly No. 6333, changed 1960), A. C. Howard Lodge, Grafton, West Virginia, 1947-1960 (Box 146, Folder 47)
      Consolidated with Lodges 1301, 561, and 560, effective Oct. 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1711. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1711 (formerly No. 6158, changed 1961), Louisville, Kentucky, 1947-1965 (Box 146, Folder 48)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 470, effective July 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 235-1713. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1713 (formerly No. 6265, changed 1961), Bert McCormick Lodge, Owensboro, Kentucky, 1944-1966 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 407, Louisville, Kentucky, effective April 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-1716. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1716, Monroe Lodge, Monroe, Louisiana, 1947-1968 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      April 28, 1947-August 12, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6085; consolidated with Lodge No. 588, Monroe, Louisiana, effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1720. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1720, C. C. Tunnage Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1945-1969 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      June 15, 1945-April 11, 1969. Formerly Lodge No. 6167; consolidated with Lodge No. 53, New Orleans, Louisiana; Lodge No. 59, New Orleans, Louisiana; and Lodge No. 1602, Cincinnati, Ohio; effective April 1, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-1726. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1726, Freight Handlers Lodge, Brunswick, Maryland, 1941-1961 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      March 21, 1941-November 8, 1961. Formerly Lodge No. 6182, Brunswick Auxiliary Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 414, Brunswick, Maryland, effective October 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1728. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1728, Detroit, Michigan, 1945-1964 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      July 6, 1945-February 12, 1964. Formerly Lodge No. 6211; consolidated with Lodge No. 160, Detroit, Michigan, effective January 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-1729. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1729, Progressive Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1943-1963 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      March 9, 1943-September 16, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6234, Michigan Central Station Cleaners Auxiliary Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 1300, Detroit, Michigan, effective July 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1731. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1731, St. Paul Union Depot Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1947-1963 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      August 5, 1947-October 24, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6328, St. Paul Union Depot Auxiliary Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 257, St. Paul, Minnesota, effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1732. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1732, Magnolia Lodge, Meridian, Mississippi, 1947-1967 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      May 29, 1947-November 16, 1967. Formerly Lodge No. 6057; consolidated with Lodges Nos. 544 and 896, Meridian, Mississippi, effective October 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1735. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1735, Amory, Mississippi, 1943-1961 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      April 13, 1943-November 8, 1961. Formerly Lodge No. 6251; consolidated with Lodge No. 1783, Memphis, Tennessee, effective October 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1737. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1737, Lone Star Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1947-1964 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      March 18, 1947-February 12, 1964. Formerly Lodge No. 6028; consolidated with Lodges Nos. 283 and 449, St. Louis, Missouri, effective January 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-1738. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1738, Apex Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1945-1961 (Box 147, Folder 11)
      September 21, 1945-October 17, 1961. Formerly Lodge No. 6037, Apex Auxiliary Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 1527, Kansas City, Missouri, effective October 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1739. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1739, Missouri Pacific, Kansas City, Missouri, 1945-1963 (Box 147, Folder 12)
      July 28, 1945-November 13, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6043, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 284, Kansas City, Missouri effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1740. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1740, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1941-1963 (Box 147, Folder 13)
      September 11, 1941-November 4, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6045, Saint Louis Lodge, changed 1960; consolidated with Lodge 554 and Lodge 280, Saint Louis, Missouri effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1742. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1742, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1947-1963 (Box 147, Folder 14)
      October 24, 1947-December 4, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6115, changed between 1959 and 1960; consolidated with Lodge 521, Saint Louis, Missouri effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1743. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1743, Missouri Lodge, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1947-1967 (Box 147, Folder 15)
      August 1, 1947-February 13, 1967. Formerly Lodge No. 6119, changed between 1957 and 1960; consolidated with Lodge 145, Saint Louis, Missouri effective January 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1744. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1744, Scout Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1944-1963 (Box 147, Folder 16)
      September 13, 1944-December 3, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6129, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 121, Kansas City, Missouri effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1745. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1745, Central District Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1943-1963 (Box 147, Folder 17)
      May 18, 1943-November 14, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6134, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 136, Kansas City, Kansas effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1746. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1746, Best Way Lodge, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1947-1966 (Box 147, Folder 18)
      July 10, 1947-March 1, 1966. Formerly Lodge No. 6164, changed between 1959 and 1960; consolidated with Lodge 524, Saint Louis, Missouri effective January 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-1747. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1747, Bando Lodge, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1945-1963 (Box 147, Folder 19)
      June 30, 1945-September 16, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6179, changed between 1959 and 1960; consolidated with Lodge 1200, East Saint Louis, Illinois effective July 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1748. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1748, Springfield, Missouri, 1947-1962 (Box 147, Folder 20)
      September 8, 1947-February 9, 1962. Formerly Lodge No. 6209, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 772, Springfield, Missouri effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1750. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1750, Progressive Lodge, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1947-1963 (Box 147, Folder 21)
      August 3, 1947-June 26, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6332, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 1740, Saint Louis, Missouri effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1752. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1752, Friendship Lodge, New York, New York, 1959-1963 (Box 147, Folder 22)
      February 12, 1959-May 8, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6118, changed between 1960 and 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1753. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1753, Pennsylvania Terminal Lodge, New York, New York, 1945-1962 (Box 147, Folder 23)
      May 15, 1945-January 19, 1962. Formerly Lodge No. 6187, consolidated with Lodge 163, New York, New York effective January 1, 1948; consolidation cancelled effective April 20, 1948, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 163, New York, New York effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1760. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1760, Asheville Lodge, Asheville, North Carolina, 1947-1966 (Box 147, Folder 24)
      October 14, 1947-September 13, 1966. Formerly Lodge No. 6106, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 313, Asheville, North Carolina effective July 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-1761. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1761, Capital City Lodge, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1945-1968 (Box 147, Folder 25)
      June 23, 1945-August 13, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6183, changed between 1960 and 1962; consolidated with Lodges 302, 334, and 2149, all Raleigh, North Carolina effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1762. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1762, Youngstown, Ohio, 1946-1962 (Box 147, Folder 26)
      March 7, 1946-January 22, 1962. Formerly Lodge No. 6014, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 489, Youngstown, Ohio and Lodge 865, Cleveland, Ohio effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1763. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1763, Friendship Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1947-1963 (Box 147, Folder 27)
      August 27, 1947-August 28, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6197, changed between 1959 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 1, Cincinnati, Ohio effective July 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1764. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1764, Scioto Valley Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1947-1963 (Box 147, Folder 28)
      January 30, 1947- December 11, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6322, changed between 1956 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 610, Columbus, Ohio effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1765. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1765, Orange Avenue Terminal Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1947-1963 (Box 147, Folder 29)
      March 18, 1947-December 11, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6325, changed between 1960 and 1962; consolidated with Lodge 725, Cleveland, Ohio effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1767. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1767, Goodwill Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1949-1962 (Box 147, Folder 30)
      February 24, 1949-February 5, 1962. Formerly Lodge No. 6340, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 803, Cleveland, Ohio effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1768. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1768, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1943-1968 (Box 147, Folder 31)
      September 13, 1943-January 3, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6257, changed between 1959 and 1963; consolidated with Lodge 777, Tulsa, Oklahoma effective October 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1769. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1769, Iron City Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1942-1961 (Box 147, Folder 32)
      January 30, 1942-December 5, 1961. Formerly Lodge No. 6017, changed between 1960 and 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1770. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1770, Greater Pittsburgh Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1943-1963 (Box 147, Folder 33)
      August 24, 1943-October 3, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6032, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 591, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania effective July 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1771. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1771, Monarch Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1945-1964 (Box 147, Folder 34)
      February 28, 1945-April 8, 1964. Formerly Lodge No. 6114, changed between 1958 and 1962; consolidated with Lodges 653 and 390, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania effective April 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-1772. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1772, Baltimore Terminal Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1942-1963 (Box 147, Folder 35)
      May 12, 1942-November 19, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6227, changed between 1959 and 1962; consolidated with Lodge 518, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania effective October 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1779. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1779, Lilly of the Valley Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1945-1959 (Box 147, Folder 36)
      June 23, 1945-November 20, 1959. Formerly Lodge No. 6007, changed after period covered in file
  - Sub-Series 235-1781. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1781, Memphis Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1946-1966 (Box 147, Folder 37)
      September 4, 1946-May 16, 1966. Formerly Lodge No. 6020, Memphis Auxiliary Lodge, changed between 1958 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 741, Memphis, Tennessee effective April 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-1782. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1782, Memphis, Tennessee, 1947-1967 (Box 147, Folder 38)
      June 25, 1947-October 2, 1967. Formerly Lodge No. 6023, changed between 1954 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 580, Memphis, Tennessee effective July 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1788. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1788, York Lodge, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1947-1966 (Box 147, Folder 39)
      August 20, 1947-June 7, 1966. Formerly Lodge No. 6202, changed between 1958 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 1152, Knoxville, Tennessee effective April 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-1789. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1789, Streamliner Lodge, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1947-1964 (Box 147, Folder 40)
      July 15, 1947-October 12, 1964. Formerly Lodge No. 6231, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 1785, Chattanooga, Tennessee effective October 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-1790. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1790, Clinchfield Lodge, Johnson City, Tennessee, 1944-1968 (Box 147, Folder 41)
      June 14, 1944-July 19, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6274, changed between 1960 and 1966; consolidated with Lodge 559, Erwin, Tennessee effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1792. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1792, King David Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1940-1968 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      July 25, 1940-October 4, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6003, changed between 1959 and 1960; consolidated with Lodge 500, Norfolk, Virginia effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1794. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1794, Alpha Lodge, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1945-1961 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      October 18, 1945-November 21, 1961. Formerly Lodge No. 6064, changed between 1960 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 1792, Norfolk, Virginia effective October 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1797. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1797, Twin City Lodge, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1947-1962 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      July 25, 1947-September 19, 1962. Formerly Lodge No. 6112, changed 1961; consolidated with Lodge 69, Richmond, Virginia effective July 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1802. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1802, Victory Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1942-1961 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      February 2, 1942-April 14, 1961. Formerly Lodge No. 6184, changed between 1958 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 302, Norfolk, Virginia effective March 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1803. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1803, Norfolk, Virginia, 1942-1963 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      June 19, 1942-March 6, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6230, changed between 1959 and 1961; consolidated with Lodge 1792, Norfolk, Virginia effective January 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-1804. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1804, Red Cap Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1948-1962 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      February 6, 1948-April 18, 1962. Formerly Lodge No. 6337, changed between 1960 and 1962; consolidated with Lodge 487, Seattle, Washington effective March 31, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2002. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2002, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1950-1961 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      April 11, 1950-May 5, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge 2066, Toronto, Ontario, Canada effective April 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-2004. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2004, Angelus Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1921-1948 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      June 20, 1921-November 19, 1948.
    - Lodge No. 2004, Angelus Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1949-1960 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      January 16, 1949-July 20, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-2005. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2005, Maryland Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1929-1962 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      November 22, 1929-November 16, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 2005, Freeport, Illinois, 1925 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      1925 October 7
  - Sub-Series 235-2008. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2008, Pioneer Express Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1922-1960 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      September 28, 1922-December 12, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-2012. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2012, Expressmen's Lodge, Waco, Texas, 1949-1961 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      January 25, 1949-February 14, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge 2125, Dallas, Texas effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-2015. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2015, Gem City Lodge, Quincy, Illinois, 1921-1962 (Box 148, Folder 13)
      October 27, 1921-April 13, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge 2094, Rock Island, Illinois effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2020. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2020, Railway Express Lodge, Willard, Ohio, 1944-1968 (Box 148, Folder 14)
      April 15, 1944-April 18, 1968. Formerly Willard Lodge; consolidated with Lodge 2006, Lima, Ohio, Lodge 2067, Toledo, Ohio and Lodge 2107, Marion, Ohio effective April 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2022. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2022, Messengers and Baggagemen Lodge, Denver, Colorado, 1926-1968 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      August 1, 1926-October 29, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge 2009, Denver, Colorado effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2024. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2024, Gateway Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1959-1963 (Box 148, Folder 16)
      June 5, 1959-November 26, 1963.
    - Lodge No. 2024, Gateway Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1921-1958 (Box 148, Folder 17)
      December 28, 1921-October 10, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-2028. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2028, North & South Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1933-1958 (Box 148, Folder 18)
      June 6, 1933-December 19, 1958.
    - Lodge No. 2028, North & South Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1924-1932 (Box 148, Folder 19)
      November 13, 1924-May 3, 1932.
  - Sub-Series 235-2029. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2029, Itaska Lodge, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1921-1957 (Box 148, Folder 20)
      December 2, 1921-December 5, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-2034. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2034, Western Express Messengers Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1923-1969 (Box 148, Folder 21)
      June 26, 1923-September 11, 1969. Members transferred and consolidated with Lodge 2184, San Francisco effective July 1, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-2035. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2035, Express Lodge, Sioux Falls, South Dakota, 1926-1960 (Box 148, Folder 22)
      May 11, 1926-November 30, 1960. Formerly Sioux Falls Expressmen Lodge; consolidated with Lodge 2085, Aberteen, South Dakota effective July 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-2037. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2037, District of Columbia Lodge, Washington, D.C., 1922-1962 (Box 148, Folder 23)
      February 24, 1922-December 18, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-2039. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2039, Lincoln Messengers Lodge, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1921-1962 (Box 148, Folder 24)
      December 2, 1921-April 13, 1962. Formerly Dynamo City Lodge; consolidated with Lodge 2057, Lincoln, Nebraska effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2040. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2040, Fulton Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1925-1958 (Box 148, Folder 25)
      December 15, 1925-September 29, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-2043. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2043, Wisconsin Lodge, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1921-1961 (Box 148, Folder 26)
      December 15, 1921-August 29, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-2044. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2044, Usona Lodge, Danbury, Connecticut, 1946-1958 (Box 148, Folder 27)
      August 30, 1946-March 1, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge 2126, Bridgeport, Connecticut effective March 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-2045. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2045, Cincinnati Express Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1922-1960 (Box 148, Folder 28)
      March 20, 1922-July 30, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-2047. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2047, Semon Lodge, Texarkana, Texas, 1950-1968 (Box 148, Folder 29)
      June 12, 1950-October 16, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge 2113, Shreveport, Louisiana effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2048. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2048, Magnolia Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1922-1957 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      January 2, 1922-November 8, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-2049. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2049, Briscoe Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1922-1958 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      August 2, 1922-November 5, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-2050. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2050, Unity Lodge, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, 1935-1960 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      May 2, 1935-November 25, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge 2066, Toronto and 2314, Edmonton effective October 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 2050, Fountain City Lodge, Fond du Lac, Wisconsin, 1921-1925 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      August 18, 1921-October 13, 1925. Disbanded
  - Sub-Series 235-2052. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2052, Tri-State Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1925-1962 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      October 31, 1925-October 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-2053. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2053, Hudson County Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1951-1966 (Box 149, Folder 5)
      January 8, 1951-March 28, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge 2147, Long Island City, New York effective March 1, 1966
    - Lodge No. 2053, Hudson County Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1948-1951 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      January 7, 1948-November 28, 1951.
    - Lodge No. 2053, Hudson County Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1946-1947 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      July 31, 1946-December 9, 1947.
    - Lodge No. 2053, Hudson County Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1929-1946 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      October 14, 1929-November 11, 1946.
    - Lodge No. 2053, Mercer Lodge, Trenton, New Jersey, 1922 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      May 1, 1922-July 6, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-2058. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2058, Biscayne Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1925-1962 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      September 8, 1925-August 20, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 2058, Elgin Lodge, Elgin, Illinois, 1923-1924 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      November 27, 1923-January 18, 1924.
  - Sub-Series 235-2059. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2059, North Gateway Lodge, Denison, Texas, 1924-1961 (Box 149, Folder 10)
      January 1, 1924-February 24, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge 2125, Dallas, Texas effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-2061. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2061, Minneapolis Express Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1922-1960 (Box 149, Folder 11)
      Oct. 5, 1922-Oct. 20, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-2062. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2062, Roger Ludlow Lodge, South Norwalk, Connecticut, 1946-1968 (Box 149, Folder 12)